This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Hunky D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
This is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will come a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Separated from the rest of his crew,
Luffy has rushed to Marineford
and straight into the epic battle between the Navy and the Whitebeard Pirates.
But will his new alliance be enough to save Ace from execution?
Attention all ships and soldiers!
Once all soldiers are in place,
we will move the schedule forward and execute Ace immediately!
That is all!
Kolic!
Luffy, no!
Let's move!
Let's go!
Wait a minute!
No!
That's the wrong side!
Ah, ahhhhhhh!
Ahhhh!
nurghh!
AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH, I'M HEEEEEEEEEEEDR!!!
Here!
Hey, is that who I think it is?
It's Crocodile.
And he's not the only one either.
Just take a look at that lineup.
Who's who on both sides.
All the big names are here.
The world can't handle this madness.
Hey Ace, sit tight, okay?
Cause we're gonna get you out of here.
Hey God, your family's messing things up again.
Luffy, no!
The grandson of our very own marine hero, Garp.
And the son of the revolutionary dragon.
I'll make that boy regret the day
he decided to become a pirate.
Where'd Crocoboy go?
Huh?
I guess the sucker chickened out
and left us high and dry.
Wait, there he is!
Damn that, you're supposed to wait for me!
Long time no see, old man.
You'll never learn.
You know, there's only one reason I'm here.
If you wanna save your brother so bad, stay out of my way.
I'm killing Whitebeard and you can't stop me.
So that old guy is Whitebeard, I thought so.
Just stay away from him!
He's Ace's friend so I'm not gonna let him get hurt!
Well, would you look at that.
It runs in the family.
You came here to rescue your big brother?
That's right.
Do you have the slightest idea who our forces are up against?
A squirt like you is gonna get slaughtered real easy.
Shut up!
You don't know, you don't even know me!
I know what you're up to.
Yeah, you wanna be the king, huh?
First you gotta go through me!
Got it!
What a cheeky little punk.
Don't come crying to me for help if you get a few boo-boos, spoiled brat.
Yeah, right!
I'm not all old like you!
I'm gonna be the one to rescue Ace!
Even if it means death!
Luffy versus the Navy!
The battle starts!
Hey, it's Luffy!
He's that famous rookie with the straw hat!
Does he have a connection to Whitebeard that we don't know of?
Damn, he's stupid!
Who breaks out of the world's greatest prison
then goes straight to Navy HQ?
Geez, if I were him, I'd be hiding under my bed right now!
He's not stupid, he's Luffy.
Huh?
This is the only way he knows.
Luffy.
Pops!
Straw hat, eh?
He's just like his brother.
Old man!
I heard something on that Navy ship I think you should know!
Look at this bonehead!
Why doesn't Whitebeard just kick his ass?
Get on with it!
He is fearless, isn't he?
Truly his father's son.
They're throwing out the schedule for an immediate execution.
Are you positive that's what you heard them say?
Yeah, they said they gotta get all set for something first, though.
But I don't know what for, cause they were using codes.
I think you wanna rescue Ace as bad as me.
And that's why I'm telling you.
Well, alright.
I suppose it's lucky I ran into you then.
Thanks, kiddo.
Sure thing.
No big deal.
Now he's talking like they're equals!
That boy has got some serious balls!
Right!
Hang on Ace, I'm on my way!
And there he goes.
Gump Gump!
Bazooka!
Get out of my way!
Well, he's Ace's brother alright.
Third Division, let's get moving!
Keep up with the boy and try to follow his lead.
Let's lend our support!
What?
Come on!
14th Division!
Let's clear a path!
We're right behind you, boss!
Luffy.
One rookie daredevil suddenly takes the lead
and they're acting like a whole new army.
Not that it matters.
Our strategy is airtight.
Don't hesitate!
Follow my orders!
So typical of Sengoku.
He probably doesn't think the execution of a mere pirate
deserves the formality of a schedule.
The big question is what they're getting set up for first.
Hey, Pops.
Just in case you haven't heard,
word on the street is they're expediting Ace's execution.
Straw Hat told me.
Our squad and the others.
They're tangled up pretty tight with the Vice Admirals at the head of the bay.
I was just about to fly over there and lend him a helping hand.
No, wait. Not yet.
Something in my gut tells me Sengoku wanted us to get that leaked info.
He wants us to advance.
Huh?
That old bastard's too clever to let his strategy get out.
Not that easily at least.
He's many things but not a fool.
Everybody climb!
A light speed kick?
Did you think I was gonna let you pass?
You fellas are awfully confident for a bunch of nobodies.
Damn!
It's Admiral Kizaru!
Huh?
Hey, you're that jerk from Sabahuti!
And you're the boy the Celestial Dragons asked me to take care of.
Nice to get his second chance.
Crap!
Straw Hat's out of his boy!
Death wins!
Make it stop, please!
I wanna go home!
What?
Whoa, Captain Buggy!
Wow, I knew you were gutsy but hot damn!
You mean you wanna kill Kizaru?
Right?
So we can go home?
Yeah, these Admirals aren't so tough.
All in a day's work for Captain Buggy!
You're all delusional!
Would you quit enabling him?
Are you still breathing, Straw Boy?
You bet!
Thanks, Eva!
See ya!
See ya?
Do you realize the only reason I'm here is to save your rubber bot?
Damn, Kizaru.
Huh?
Wait, is that...
Kuma?
Hey, that's the big guy that blew my friends away and shot me across the sea!
Now rolling...
Faa!
Bartholomew Kuma!
You heartless scoundrel!
I understand you have a role to play as Warlord, but still...
All these years we've been friends and now you fire a laser at me?
Are you even looking at who you are?
Ah!
My hair!
Ima!
Quit caulking!
Don't worry, I've got this under control!
Just let me handle it and run those skinny legs to Ace!
If you say so!
Now, let's do this!
Ima!
Yeah!
harios
Who你好 buscarled
Me!
Are you even looking at who you are?
Ema!
Are you even looking at who you are!
Ah, ah, aah!
My hair!
Ima!
Quit caulking!
Don't worry, I've got this under control!
Just let me handle it and run those skinny legs to Ace!
If you say so!
Now...
Let's do this!
Sorry, but your luck got away from you when you ran into us.
Well, Straw Hat, might as well lie down because this is where you die.
Do I know you?
Ha! I'm full-body!
I've been waiting a long time to make you pay for what happened at the Baratier.
Oh, right. Sanji kicked your ass there.
This chakram. I'm sure it'll ring a few bells for you.
Yeah, you're the hypno guy from Usopp's village. What are you doing with these guys?
I joined the Navy to hone my skills, and I've mastered the art of hypnotism.
It's twice as effective yielding two chakrams.
When I say one, two, Django, you'll fall into a deep sleep.
One, two, Django!
Worthless sacks of crap.
So disappointing.
You're that cage chick from Alabaster, right? I don't have time to play games with you people!
I never play games.
Come on, Oslee, cage!
Anyone who tries to pass through me will be bound by the bars of my black cage.
I love it when she uses that line, Captain Hina's the essence of captivating.
I'm done spending time behind bars!
Now, second gear!
So fast, I couldn't follow.
Hina failed.
You're not the only one who failed.
Captain Hina's truly taken us captive now, both body and soul.
Don't take on the Vice-Admirals alone!
They're too strong for one man!
Hey, Captain Squart!
Looks like things are getting ugly inside the bay!
I've noticed!
I gotta get to Ace fast before it gets worse.
At least Orr's opened up a path for me.
There's a good chance I can outspot him if I sneak in through here.
Huh?
I know you.
Why do they all have to be so strong?
Ah!
Ha!
Look at him go.
He's as high-spirited as ever I see.
Oh, yeah.
I can cut off his shadow again and then plant it inside the new zombie.
Rise, my zombie soldiers!
It's time!
Now then, are you listening?
Good!
Capture Straw Hat and bring him to me.
I want him alive!
Stupid Moria!
I don't want to deal with that creep now!
You keep up!
There are more of them!
Of course!
We are standing on a battlefield.
I've got plenty of fresh corpses gathered about to pick and choose from.
Capture Straw Hat Luffy!
He's the one that caused that jailbreak!
That's right.
Keep going.
This should be enough officers to keep the kid busy.
He can't keep bouncing around like that forever.
Luffy!
Stay back!
What the hell do you think you're doing?
You became a pirate because I wanted to!
You only went to sea because you were following me!
But I've got my own damn life without you in it!
I've already got enough of my own friends!
Ace...
You get it?
I want you to stay the hell away from me!
You really want to save me?
A scrawny whip like you?
Luffy!
What makes you think I'd even want something like that, huh?
That's just humiliating!
Go home, Luffy!
I didn't ask for this!
I'm begging you.
Please.
I can't let you die here with me.
It's my fault.
It's...
It's all my fault.
Ace!
You're my brother!
It's the truth.
All it takes to become brothers
is to share some sake.
From here on out,
we're honest-to-goodness brothers.
Did I just hear them say that they're brothers?
So then he's also Roger's son?
But both of Ace's parents were dead when he was born.
That can be possible, can't it?
I don't give a damn what you want!
I'm here to save you!
You stubborn jackass!
Move out, zombie soldiers!
Attack and capture!
Seawater!
Jinbei!
They came from devil fruit powers,
and thus, they are weak to the sea.
Press on.
These zombies will prove no match for me.
Okay, if you're sure.
First son of the sea, Jinbei.
We've got to fight a warlord.
You're making a mockery of the Navy
by letting this rookie take control of things!
Let me at him.
I'll crush this squirt into paste.
Make no mistake,
he's a tooth-thread in the making.
He was raised alongside Firefist Ace
as his stepbrother.
And if that's not bad enough,
he's the biological son
of the revolutionary dragon!
Did he just say what I think he said?
He's the son of the worst criminal in history!
Makes you think twice about who you punch, huh?
Why didn't anyone tell me that's his dad?
Now they know!
Oh, man!
Luffy,
it wouldn't bother me
if your father was the devil himself.
I had no idea.
Well, damn.
Okay!
Gum-gum pistol!
I finally understand
what happened at Log Town.
It only makes sense
that dragon would save his own son.
Did you hear what he just said?
Does he mean the dragon?
Head office!
Can you hear me?
I'm calling from Sabaody!
I've got huge news!
We're talking worldwide headlines here!
I guess we'll just have to kill him, too!
I can't let him survive!
Who cares?
There's no reason to hide it any longer.
And it's not like it's gonna make his life any worse
since he's already a notorious outlaw.
You two brothers are both damn fools.
Dirt gear!
Gum-gum-gum!
Giant!
Ripple!
Ice!
Ace!
Say whatever mean stuff you want!
I'm still gonna save you!
Oh, hell yeah.
Your brother speaks for every one of us, Ace.
Yeah, we're all a part of your family, too.
And nothing's gonna stop us.
Hey, Marco, don't let that kid die no matter what.
You got it.
Luffy.
As Ace watches helplessly while the battle unfolds before him, he comes to an important decision, though he's unable to act.
Meanwhile, a flurry of friends, foes, and fantastic powers explodes on the battlefield.
On the next, One Piece, hard battles, one after another, Devil Fruit Eaters versus Devil Fruit Eaters.
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!